question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The word 'Inception' came from the 2010 blockbuster hit 'Inception'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the original script of 'The Matrix', the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "'Foodfight!' earned less than $80,000 at box office.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "'Minions' was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, 'Bad Motherf*cker' in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, 'Chewbacca', is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004's 'The Aviator'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
